{
  "questions": [
    {
      "index": 1,
      "question": "Who is often referred to as the 'King of Bollywood'?",
      "options": [
        "Aamir Khan",
        "Shah Rukh Khan",
        "Salman Khan",
        "Akshay Kumar",
        "Amitabh Bachchan",
        "Hrithik Roshan",
        "Ranbir Kapoor",
        "Ajay Devgn",
        "Ranveer Singh",
        "Saif Ali Khan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "index": 2,
      "question": "Which Bollywood movie is known for the famous dialogue 'Mere paas maa hai'?",
      "options": [
        "Sholay",
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Deewaar",
        "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
        "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai",
        "Zindagi Na Milegi Dobara",
        "Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna",
        "Kabhi Haan Kabhi Naa",
        "Dhoom 2",
        "Darr"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "index": 3,
      "question": "In the movie 'Kuch Kuch Hota Hai,' which character famously wore a red saree and was called 'Miss Braganza'?",
      "options": [
        "Anjali Sharma",
        "Rahul Khanna",
        "Tina Malhotra",
        "Aman Mathur",
        "Principal Malhotra",
        "Naina Kapoor",
        "Pooja Sharma",
        "Rani Mukerji",
        "Shah Rukh Khan",
        "Salman Khan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "index": 4,
      "question": "Which Bollywood actor is known for his role as 'Bhuvan' in the movie 'Lagaan'?",
      "options": [
        "Aamir Khan",
        "Shah Rukh Khan",
        "Salman Khan",
        "Akshay Kumar",
        "Amitabh Bachchan",
        "Hrithik Roshan",
        "Ranbir Kapoor",
        "Ajay Devgn",
        "Ranveer Singh",
        "Saif Ali Khan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "index": 5,
      "question": "Which 1994 Bollywood movie featured the hit song 'Tujhe Dekha Toh Yeh Jaana Sanam'?",
      "options": [
        "Kabhi Haan Kabhi Naa",
        "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
        "Dil To Pagal Hai",
        "Hum Aapke Hain Koun..!",
        "Mohra",
        "Andaaz Apna Apna",
        "Rangeela",
        "Karan Arjun",
        "Kuch Kuch Hota Hai",
        "Darr"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "index": 6,
      "question": "Which Bollywood actress is known for her role as 'Chandni' in the movie of the same name?",
      "options": [
        "Madhuri Dixit",
        "Kajol",
        "Sridevi",
        "Rani Mukerji",
        "Kareena Kapoor Khan",
        "Aishwarya Rai Bachchan",
        "Priyanka Chopra",
        "Deepika Padukone",
        "Alia Bhatt",
        "Juhi Chawla"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "index": 7,
      "question": "Who played the role of 'Mogambo' in the Bollywood movie 'Mr. India'?",
      "options": [
        "Amrish Puri",
        "Pran",
        "Prem Chopra",
        "Danny Denzongpa",
        "Ranjeet",
        "Ajit Khan",
        "Kader Khan",
        "Shakti Kapoor",
        "Paresh Rawal",
        "Gulshan Grover"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "index": 8,
      "question": "In the movie 'Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham,' what is the nickname of Shah Rukh Khan's character?",
      "options": [
        "Rahul",
        "Raj",
        "Rohit",
        "Kabir",
        "Aman",
        "Dev",
        "Arjun",
        "Vicky",
        "Sameer",
        "Karan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "index": 9,
      "question": "Which Bollywood actress is often referred to as the 'Queen of Bollywood'?",
      "options": [
        "Deepika Padukone",
        "Priyanka Chopra",
        "Aishwarya Rai Bachchan",
        "Kareena Kapoor Khan",
        "Kangana Ranaut",
        "Alia Bhatt",
        "Madhuri Dixit",
        "Kajol",
        "Rani Mukerji",
        "Sridevi"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 4
    },
    {
      "index": 10,
      "question": "Who is the director of the Bollywood movie 'Dil Chahta Hai'?",
      "options": [
        "Karan Johar",
        "Farhan Akhtar",
        "Sanjay Leela Bhansali",
        "Rajkumar Hirani",
        "Rohit Shetty",
        "Aditya Chopra",
        "Zoya Akhtar",
        "Anurag Kashyap",
        "Imtiaz Ali",
        "Rakeysh Omprakash Mehra"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "index": 11,
      "question": "Which Bollywood actor is known for his role as 'Don' in the movie of the same name?",
      "options": [
        "Aamir Khan",
        "Shah Rukh Khan",
        "Salman Khan",
        "Akshay Kumar",
        "Amitabh Bachchan",
        "Hrithik Roshan",
        "Ranbir Kapoor",
        "Ajay Devgn",
        "Ranveer Singh",
        "Saif Ali Khan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "index": 12,
      "question": "In the movie 'Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge,' what is the name of the character played by Kajol?",
      "options": [
        "Simran",
        "Anjali",
        "Pooja",
        "Naina",
        "Meera",
        "Geet",
        "Kiran",
        "Zara",
        "Rani",
        "Radha"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "index": 13,
      "question": "Which Bollywood actor is known for his role as 'Bajrangi' in the movie 'Bajrangi Bhaijaan'?",
      "options": [
        "Aamir Khan",
        "Shah Rukh Khan",
        "Salman Khan",
        "Akshay Kumar",
        "Amitabh Bachchan",
        "Hrithik Roshan",
        "Ranbir Kapoor",
        "Ajay Devgn",
        "Ranveer Singh",
        "Saif Ali Khan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "index": 14,
      "question": "Who is the female lead in the Bollywood movie 'Chennai Express'?",
      "options": [
        "Kajol",
        "Priyanka Chopra",
        "Deepika Padukone",
        "Kareena Kapoor Khan",
        "Kangana Ranaut",
        "Alia Bhatt",
        "Madhuri Dixit",
        "Sridevi",
        "Rani Mukerji",
        "Aishwarya Rai Bachchan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "index": 15,
      "question": "In the movie 'Kabhi Alvida Naa Kehna,' which character is played by Amitabh Bachchan?",
      "options": [
        "Dev Saran",
        "Maya Talwar",
        "Rhea Saran",
        "Rishi Talwar",
        "Kamal Mehra",
        "Neelam Mehra",
        "Kamal Kumar",
        "Sanjay Kapoor",
        "Preity Zinta",
        "Abhishek Bachchan"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 4
    }
  ]
}
